Our society succeeded in quantifying
people's psychological and mental states.
（朱(あかね)）私たちの社会は―
人の心理や精神状態の計測に
成功した
Based on the Psycho-Pass,
the numerical value of the soul,
魂の数値 サイコパスに基づき―
people can be judged
before they commit crimes.
人々は罪を犯す前に裁かれる
They are judged by the Ministry
of Welfare's massive surveillance network,
審判を下すのは―
厚生省の
巨大な監視ネットワーク―
the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステム
Thanks to this system
and a long policy of isolation,
このシステムと
長い鎖国政策により―
Japan escaped the tragedy of global strife
and became the only peaceful nation.
日本は世界紛争の悲劇を免れ
唯一の平和な国となった
But at what cost?
だが そのために私たちは―
何を犠牲にし そして
何を忘れ去ったのだろうか
What have we forgotten?
The answers are shrouded in darkness,
答えは 深い闇の中にある
along with the true crimes
that lurk in our society.
この社会に潜む本当の罪と共に
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
♪～
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the lost memories that flee
once they're liberated and banished
Are an everlasting cubism.
Cause I know that in a future gone mad,
Even nightmares are peaceful.
RESET, RESET, yeah.
The midnight sun awakens
and turns to a riot.
A gun for a faux-friendly kiss.
A knife for a faux-revolutionary hug.
Get rid of it all, even the frozen chains.
Reality is always outside your head.
In a world seen through bestial eyes,
There is neither darkness nor light.
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the false memories that flash before
your eyes impatiently and impulsively
Are an everlasting cubism.
～♪
#01 Laelaps' Calling
（ノイズ）
（リックのうめき声）
I'm sorry,
（リック）すまない
うっ うう… アーディレ…
Adele.
（ハッチの開く音）
（リック）あっ… はっ！
うわあ！　あー！
We get to see one of the world's largest
transport drones! What a time to be alive.
（ドローンマニア）
世界最大級の輸送ドローンが―
国内で拝めるなんて
いい時代になりましたね
It's here.
（ドローンマニア）
あっ 来ましたよ
It is? About time.
おっ 待ってました
It crashed.
（ドローンマニア）落ちたぞ…
（ドローンマニア）ウソだろ おい
You're kidding, right?
How artistic.
（梓澤(あずさわ)）芸術だなあ
"I'm happy."
（梓澤）アイムハッピー
（シャッター音）
The Ministry of Welfare
has declined to reveal
（キャスター）
公安局 局長が… された事件で―
（ノイズ）
the Psycho-Pass
of Ex-Inspector —— ——,
（ノイズ）
厚生省は 現行犯逮捕された…
who was arrested for the ——
—— —— of Public Safety.
元監視官のサイコパスを非公表と…
（ノイズ）
It's my first day on the job.
（灼(あらた)）今日から仕事なんだ
It's finally starting, Dad.
やっと始まるよ 父さん
Your Psycho-Pass is ——.
（篤志(あつし)）お前のサイコパスは…
This is all to protect you
from the —— ——.
すべては… お前を守る…
I'll find...
必ず見つけるよ
the truth.
真実を
Arata.
（炯(けい)）灼 灼
Hey, Arata.
（炯）おい 灼
（灼）んん… ん…
（灼）ん～？
（炯）じきに到着だ
We're almost there.
Get it together.
（炯）しゃっきりしろ
You'll be directing latent criminals.
今日から潜在犯を部下にするんだぞ
（あくび）
They're just people.
人間だよ 普通の
They have high crime coefficients.
Call me if they give you trouble.
（炯）高い犯罪係数を持つ連中だ
何かあったら すぐに呼べ
Don't worry, Kei.
心配ないよ 炯
It's not like latent criminals
have actually committed any crimes.
潜在犯ったって 実際に
罪を犯したわけじゃないんだし
Don't let our bosses hear you say that.
そんなこと
上官の前で口にするなよ
（あくび）
（灼）はーい はい
Yes, sir.
Your symptoms again?
また症状が出たのか？
I tried to get some shut-eye,
but I couldn't.
ベッドで寝ようとしたけど
ダメだった
Spend more on psychological care.
もっとメンタルケアに金をかけろ
If that was all it took,
we wouldn't be here today, right?
それで済むなら
今日 こうしてない… だろ？
Yeah. This is our first step.
ああ これが最初の一歩だ
The Drone Administration Bureau
claims that the cause
（細呂木(ほそろぎ)）開国政策で
人の輸送が急務となり―
was hastily overhauling cargo drones
for passenger use
貨物機を人間用に
急ごしらえしたせいだと―
due to demand created by anti-isolation.
ドローン管理局が
言い立てているよ
So, an isolationist excuse
and a report to go with it?
（霜月(しもつき)）鎖国主義者らしい
言い訳ついでに通報ですか
They believe the passengers may riot.
（細呂木）乗客が
暴動を起こす恐れがあるとね
Seems their view of immigrants
hasn't changed.
まだ入国者に そうしたイメージを
抱いているらしい
So, are you an anti-isolationist?
時に 君は開国主義者かね？
Whatever the case may be, it boils
down to what suits the Sibyl System.
（霜月）鎖国であれ開国であれ
重要なのは―
シビュラシステムにとって
理想的か否かです
A wise answer.
（細呂木）至言だな
On those grounds,
I question our deployment.
（霜月）その点
我々の出動は疑問です
It could cause a mental hazard.
かえってメンタル･ハザードが
起きかねません
Find a chance to hand it off
to Drone Administration.
頃合いを見て ドローン管理局に
引き継がせればいい
They owe us a favor.
あちらに貸し１つだ
Foreign Affairs isn't here.
（霜月）外務省の連中は
来てませんね
They weren't called.
（細呂木）彼らに要請はない
Worried?
気になるか？
（車の走行音）
（車のドアの閉まる音）
Inspector Arata Shindo.
I'm taking up my post today.
本日より着任
慎導(しんどう) 灼監視官です
Inspector Kei Mikhail Ignatov. Likewise.
同じく
炯･ミハイル･イグナトフ監視官
Good. I have high hopes for you.
ふむ 期待しているよ
I'll leave the rest to you,
Chief Shimotsuki.
では あとは頼むよ 霜月課長
Yes, Bureau Chief Hosorogi.
（霜月）はい 細呂木局長
（炯）あ…
I'm not a holo.
私はホロじゃないわよ
Let's start with the initial assessment.
では早速 事故の初期調査を
You are to direct enforcers
to control the situation,
乗客である入国者のメンタルケア
including providing psychological care
to the immigrant passengers.
その他 事態の収拾を
各執行官に指示しなさい
And don't forget to bring Dominators.
それと
ドミネーターの携行を忘れずに
Dominators? You want us to go armed?
ドミネーター… 武装せよと？
By another bureau's request, I order you
to suppress the immigrants if they riot.
他局の要請に基づき―
入国者が暴動を起こした場合の
速やかな鎮圧を命じます
Understood.
了解しました
Inspector Shindo, you are
to use your Mentalist skills.
慎導監視官は
メンタリストとしての技能を―
And Inspector Ignatov, use your military
experience to expedite your duties.
イグナトフ監視官は
軍事経験を生かし―
円滑な職務の遂行を期待します
I have to contact Ariake Airport,
so the scene is in your hands.
私は有明(ありあけ)空港の管理者と
話をするので―
現場は任せるわね
Yes, Chief Shimotsuki, ma'am.
はい 霜月課長
Don't sleep with your eyes open.
（灼）あっ
（炯）目を開けたまま寝るな
（あくび）
Jeez.
ったく
The new inspectors are starting today,
aren't they?
（雛河(ひなかわ)）新人の監視官
今日からですね
Can you believe one's an immigrant?
Public Safety's not what it used to be.
（天馬(てんま)）１人は移民ってマジか？
公安も地に落ちたもんだぜ
The immigrant quotas you hear about?
（入江(いりえ)）
はやりの入国者枠ってやつでしょ
How much do you think he paid
for a Public Safety job?
（入江）公安局のポスト買うのに
いくら払ったんだか
If he can handle the work,
who he is doesn't matter.
（如月(きさらぎ)）仕事さえできるなら
誰でもいい
Enforcers, from this day forth,
we will be your supervisors.
（炯）執行官の諸君
本日より我々が君たちを監督する
Our orders are absolute, and in principle,
we do not accept questions.
我々の命令が絶対であり
原則として質問は受けつけない
Yeah, yeah. We know.
はいはい
んなこた分かってますよ
Give us your "absolute orders," Inspector.
（入江）
絶対的指示ってやつをください
監視官
Well then, activate your Dominators.
では ドミネーターを
起動してください
Do we need them to investigate a crash?
必要ですか？
事故の調査でしょう？
I said no questions.
“質問はなし”と言った
Another bureau requested it.
他局からの要請です
Let's pray we won't need them.
必要ないことを祈りましょ
Dominator Portable
（ドミネーター）携帯型心理診断
鎮圧執行システム ドミネーター
Psychological Diagnosis
and Suppression System has been activated.
起動しました
User authentication,
Inspector Arata Shindo.
ユーザー認証 慎導 灼監視官
Inspector Kei Mikhail Ignatov.
炯･ミハイル･イグナトフ監視官
Enforcer Temma Todoroki.
廿六木(とどろき)天馬執行官
Enforcer Kazumichi Irie.
入江一途(かずみち)執行官
Enforcer Mao Kisaragi.
如月真緒(まお)執行官
Enforcer Sho Hinakawa.
雛河 翔(しょう)執行官
Public Safety Bureau
Criminal Investigation Department,
公安局刑事課所属
使用許諾 確認
Dominator usage approval confirmed.
Valid user.
適正ユーザーです
Well?
（炯）どうだった？
（灼）見てのとおりさ
The two would-be tough guys
are planning to trip us up.
こわもてぶってる２人が
邪魔をする気だ
The woman and the thin guy
are watching how we act.
女性と痩せてるほうは
俺たちの出方を見てる
I'll take the shady guys
and monitor the rescuees.
危ないのは俺が担当して
救助者を監視する
You examine the drone.
灼は機体の調査を頼む
Got it.
了解
You'd die if you fell in this, huh?
（灼）これ
落ちたら死ぬんですよね？
It's contaminated water.
Want to give it a try?
汚染水ですから
（如月）落ちてみます？
（灼）え？
Very funny.
（灼）ご冗談を
んん… うわっ
（振動音）
That scared me!
怖っ
（雛河）ああ…
（如月）しっかりしてください
Get a hold of yourself.
Everyone, please get in line.
皆さん 列に並んでください
And no cutting.
割り込まないで
How long will this take?
Please hurry.
It won't take long, so please get in line.
すぐ行いますから 列に並んで
Why are you running
Psycho-Pass Hue Checks?
（外国人）なぜ
サイコパスの色相チェックを行う？
Our Crime Coefficients were fine
at the immigration check.
入国審査時に
犯罪係数の問題はなかったはずだ
Please get back in line
and wait your turn.
（局員）列に戻って
順番をお待ちください
We have permanent residency.
Why do we get treated differently?
（外国人）我々だって
永住権を取得してるんだぞ
なぜ対応が違うんだ？
It's regulation. Please wait your turn.
（局員）規則ですので
お待ちください
Temma.
天(てん)さん
（天馬）ヘッ
Have the airport send interpretation
devices and mental care drones for them.
彼らに
人数分の通訳デバイスと―
メンタルケアドローンを
空港から回してください
Why me? That's not my job.
（局員）何で うちが？
それは私の仕事ではない
（炯）ん…
（女性の悲鳴）
（炯）あっ
They've pulled guns on us.
（外国人）銃を向けたぞ
Hey!
ちょっと
What are you doing?
何をしている！
We can speed things up with these.
これでチェックすりゃ
早いでしょうが
Any latent criminals here?
（入江）潜在犯はいねえか？
執行しちまうぞ
We'll enforce you.
（外国人）はっ！
No!
（外国人）ああっ
（外国人）やめろ！
うわっ
Crime Coefficient is over 100.
（ドミネーター）
犯罪係数 オーバー100
Enforcement mode is Non-Lethal Paralyzer.
執行モード
ノンリーサル パラライザー
Take careful aim
慎重に照準を定め
対象を制圧してください
- and subdue the target.
- See? He's a bad guy.
慎重に照準を定め
対象を制圧してください
ほら 悪いのがいた
（銃声）
（外国人）うっ
Nobody move!
全員 動くな！
Time out, Inspector.
たんま たんま 監視官
We were just doing our jobs.
俺たちゃ 仕事しただけですよ
あっ
Don't act without permission.
I'll enforce you two next time.
勝手なまねはするな
次は お前たちから執行する
Get as many mental care drones
as possible ASAP.
メンタルケアドローンを
今すぐ あるだけ回すように
Understood?
（炯）いいですね？
（局員）は… はい
Y-Yes, sir.
Is the evacuation complete?
（灼）避難は すべて完了かな？
One person unaccounted for.
（コミッサ）１名 足りません
Mr. Asahi Rick Fellows' status is unknown.
旭(あさひ)･リック･フェロウズさんの
安否が不明です
He's an accountant for Hyper Transport Co.
（如月）
ハイパー･トランスポート社の
会計士ですね
Employees should have received
priority care.
社員なら
優先的にケアされているはず
（灼）ん～
According to the records,
Rick was in this seat.
記録では
リックさんは この席にいた
It's broken.
壊れてる
（ノイズ）
So is this.
これも
（においを嗅ぐ音）
（灼）ん～？
Inspector?
（雛河）監視官？
（如月）寝る気ですか？
Are you sleeping?
It's raining.
雨が降ってる
（雛河･如月）ん？
（リック）うっ うわー！
ハァ ハァ… んっ んん…
うっ うわっ う… うっ ハァ…
ハァ… ああー！
（雛河･如月）あっ
I'm going to be killed.
（灼）俺は… 殺される…
（雛河･如月）え？
（リックの荒い息）
（リック）あっ ああ…
あっ
What is he doing?
（如月）何してるの？
I don't know.
（雛河）分かりません
I'm sorry.
すまない…
はっ！
（リック）うわあ！　あー！
（雛河）あ… あっ
（如月のため息）
Do you want to die?
死ぬ気ですか！
We've got to save him!
早く助けないと！　早く！
Hurry!
（ローター音）
（灼）はっ はっ…
ハァッ はっ…
（くしゃみ）
I heard you almost drowned yourself,
you idiot.
入水寸前だと聞いたぞ このバカ
（鼻をすする音）
（灼）すぐバカって言う
You're quick to call me an idiot.
I just took a little dip.
ちょっと潜っただけ
Don't do a Mental Trace on a dead man
when I'm not there to hold your rope.
俺がロープを握ってない時に―
死人の
メンタルトレースなんてするな
It's a shame we were too late.
（灼）手遅れだったなんて…
残念だよ
Was it an accidental death?
状況的には事故死か
No, that doesn't add up.
（灼）いや おかしい
（炯）ん？
He was frightened before the crash.
その人 墜落の前から怖がってた
That's why he left his seat and ran away.
それで座席を離れて
逃げ出したんだ
He couldn't call for help
due to a device error.
デバイスのエラーで
助けも呼べなかった
His employer was on board as well.
Let's ask him about it.
彼の雇用主も搭乗していた
早速 話を聞こう
We've got a weirdo, huh?
変なのが来ちゃったわね
But he found a missing person.
でも消えた人間を見つけ出した
Probably coincidence.
たまたまでしょ
あ…
What were you thinking?
（与根原(よねはら)）君ら 何考えてんの？
Public Safety doesn't need to mobilize
for an accident!
ただの事故で
公安局が出てくる必要ないでしょ
Mr. Yonehara,
this was an official request.
（炯）与根原さん
これは正式な要請です
We just discovered one casualty.
先ほど 死亡者１名を発見しました
Do you mind?
よろしければ お話を
Of course I mind. Care takes priority.
（与根原）よろしいわけある？
ケア優先でしょ
What if my Psycho-Pass clouds up?
サイコパス曇ったら
どうしてくれんの？
（灼）んん…
（与根原）あ？
Crime Coefficient is 41.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数 41
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
執行対象ではありません
トリガーをロックします
（与根原）う… ああ…
（灼）クリアだ
He's clear.
Idiot.
（炯）バカ…
（与根原）うっ
You've got to be kidding me!
Don't you know who I am?
ふざけんな！
俺を誰だと思ってんの？
I'll lodge a complaint!
（与根原）厳重に抗議するからね！
（灼）あ…
（舌打ち）
He's gone.
行っちゃった
What did you expect? So?
当たり前だ
It's obvious he's hiding something.
（炯）で？
（灼）顔に出てた
何か知ってる
But his Psycho-Pass was clear.
だがサイコパスはクリアだった
うーん
What are the inspectors doing?
（雛河）何してるんでしょう？
監視官たち
Having a good time.
（入江）浮かれてんだろ
They think Criminal Investigations
is the elite track.
刑事課を
エリートコースだと思ってさ
Damn officials are all the same.
クソ役人が どいつも一緒だぜ
Hopefully they don't die in accidents,
like before.
前みたいに
事故って死ななきゃいいんだが
Hey, watch your mouth.
ちょっと めったなこと言わないで
Don't bring that up again.
その話題は やめとけ
Yeah, yeah. My bad.
へいへい 悪かったよ
Shizuka Homura.
I'll be joining you as of today.
（静火(しずか)）本日より同席します
法斑(ほむら)静火です
Haruki Shirogane. Welcome.
（代銀(しろがね)）代銀遙熙(はるき)だ 歓迎するよ
Kyoko Saionji. You're awfully young.
（裁園寺(さいおんじ)）裁園寺莢子(きょうこ)よ
ずいぶん若いのね
Roundrobin Proceedings Management
Middleware, activated.
（ラウンドロビン）
議事進行ミドルウェア
ラウンドロビン起動
User authentication, Shizuka Homura.
ユーザー認証 法斑静火
Congressman is a valid user.
コングレスマン 適正ユーザーです
Now, Roundrobin, begin.
（代銀）さあ ラウンドロビン
始めてくれ
Case No. 10779, relation start.
（ラウンドロビン）
第一〇七七九号事案
リレーション スタート
I'm the dealer.
（代銀）親は私だ ジョイン
Join.
（裁園寺）ジョイン
（静火）ジョイン
Join.
Maintain participation
until the relation concludes.
（ラウンドロビン）
リレーション完結まで
参加を継続してください
Absence or obstruction
are targets for enforcement.
欠席や妨害行為は
執行対象になります
Welcome to Bifrost.
ようこそ ビフロストへ
Let us wager true freedom and power
in this society
この社会での真の自由と
権力を賭けて―
on a thrilling game.
心躍るゲームをしようじゃないか
I'd love to.
望むところです
What were you thinking?
It's your first day!
（霜月）着任早々 何してるの！
Reckless use of a Dominator
at a rescue scene?
救助現場で
不用意にドミネーターを使用！
Contact with contaminated water?
高濃度汚染水に接触！
Do you think you're
in a slapstick cat-and-mouse comedy?
あんたたち 猫とネズミの―
ドタバタコメディーでも
してるつもり？
Take this seriously!
真剣にやりなさい！
About that.
その件ですが…
We have suspicions about the deceased.
Permission to investigate?
死亡者に不審な点があります
捜査を
Denied.
却下
（灼）あ…
Hyper Transport
lodged a formal complaint.
（霜月）
ハイパー･トランスポート社から
猛抗議を受けたわ
Drone Administration will take over
the case. Resume normal duties.
調査はドローン管理局が引き継ぐ
通常勤務に就きなさい
In that case,
（灼）ではですね…
（霜月）んっ
may we file a report with Drone
Administration during our duties?
通常勤務の際 ドローン管理局に
意見書を提出するというのは？
A report?
（霜月）意見書？
Yes, ma'am.
With data from our investigation.
はい 今回の事故調査データを―
We'll assess the risks
from our department's standpoint.
公安局刑事課の観点から
リスク評価します
I can live with that.
まあ それくらいなら
We might ask around a little.
少し話を聞いて回るかも
しれませんが…
Not a problem.
（霜月）問題ありません
（炯･灼）ありがとうございます
Thank you, ma'am.
（志恩(しおん)）ウフッ
（ドアの開く音）
Excuse us.
（炯）失礼します
（灼）こんにちは
Hello.
Welcome. You must be the new guys.
いらっしゃい 新人のお二人さん
Shion Karanomori, analyst,
at your service.
分析官の唐之杜(からのもり)志恩よ よろしく
（灼）あっ わあ
You're even prettier than I heard!
こんな美人だなんて
ウワサ以上ですね フフッ
Oh, really?
あら そう？
I hate to cut to the chase,
but did you hear about the crash?
早速ですが
事故の件 ご存じですか？
Well, more or less.
（志恩）まあ ひととおりは
Please investigate the cause of the crash,
事故原因 トランスポート社
被害者と同社役員
the transport company, the victims,
and the company officials.
以上の調査を願います
But it's not a crime, is it?
でも事件じゃないんでしょう？
We're writing a report,
（灼）意見書作りですよ
in order to manage risks and prevent
future crashes before they happen.
リスク管理に努め―
今後 こうした事故を
未然に防ぐためです
ふーん まあ 問題なさそうね
That shouldn't be a problem.
By the way, we should organize
a welcoming party for you two.
それはそうと
あなたたちの歓迎会やらなきゃ
うわあ ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
We'll help.
自分たちも手伝います
Then it wouldn't be much of
a welcoming party.
それじゃ歓迎会になんないでしょ
（灼）あ…
You elite inspectors
should maintain your distance.
エリート監視官様は
大きく構えてりゃいいの
I see.
（灼）アハッ
（炯）はあ…
Well then, pleased to meet you!
では よろしくお願いします！
（灼の鼻歌）
They're both bending your orders.
２人そろって課長命令を曲解
We've got some fun ones, huh,
Chief Shimotsuki?
面白いのが来ましたね 霜月課長
They're certainly capable.
（霜月）有能なのは間違いない
I'll give them a long leash as long as
they don't break regulations. Help them.
規定に違反しないかぎり
遊撃させる
サポートしてあげて
Roger that.
（志恩）了解
Chief Shimotsuki tacitly approving
unauthorized action?
あの霜月課長が
独断行動を黙認…
Something really must be up.
これ ホントに訳ありね
Personnel only. No admittance.
A crazy rich kid and a stuck-up
foreigner? I can't stand 'em.
ああ～ 浮かれたボンボンに―
偉そうな外国人だぜ
気に食わねえ
Want me to see if I can find
some dirt on them?
（入江）何か弱みでもないか
調べとくか？
Hey, nerdy boy.
（天馬）よう オタク小僧
You can dig some up, right?
（天馬）調べられるよな？
（雛河）え… 僕が？
Me?
It's your fault the rich kid survived.
お前らのせいで
ボンボンは無事だったんだろうが
You should've sunk him in the sea.
Not enough to kill him.
ちゃんと海に沈めとけ
死なない程度に
What do you mean, "should've"?
“ちゃんと”って何ですか？
（天馬）あ？
（天馬）このっ このっ
（雛河）イテテ…
（サイレン）
（天馬）ん？
Psycho-Pass exceeding permissible
values in Haneda, Ota.
（アナウンス）大田(おおた)区羽田(はねだ)で
規定値超過のサイコパスを計測
Inspectors on duty, proceed to the scene
with Enforcers.
当直監視官は
執行官と急行してください
（入江）ん？
当直監視官は
執行官と急行してください
"On duty"? Isn't that us?
当直って うちじゃねえの？
They haven't scheduled
the Enforcer shifts yet.
（雛河）まだ執行官のシフト
決まってない…
Perfect. You go.
（天馬）ちょうどいい
お前 行ってこい
Why me?
何で僕が… うう…
（サイレン）
Does this really call for two inspectors?
（如月）監視官が
２人とも出る必要あります？
We want to get used to the job.
早く現場に慣れたくてね
それよりも―
More importantly, immigrant trouble
seems to be on the rise.
最近 入国者のトラブルが
増えてるようだな？
Yes. Because more residential districts
are accepting immigrants,
ええ 確かに 入国者を受け入れる
住宅地が増えた影響で―
we're mobilizing more often.
出動回数が増加しています
How can he sleep next to
an Enforcer on duty?
勤務中に
執行官の隣で寝るなんて…
Most inspectors don't?
そんな監視官は珍しいか？
Not really. I don't know whether
to call him bold or unconventional.
まあ 大胆というか 型破りというか
Please wake up, Inspector Shindo.
起きてください 慎導監視官
（灼）んん…
Speaking of unconventional, I hear there
was an inspector like that in Unit 1.
（炯）型破りといえば―
昔 一係の監視官が
そうだったらしいな
You mean Ex-Inspector Tsunemori?
常守(つねもり)元監視官ですか？
You know her?
知ってるのか？
No. I didn't become an enforcer
until after that incident.
いえ 私が執行官になったのは
例の事件のあとで
Only Hinakawa has experience
working with her.
一緒に働いた経験があるのは
雛河だけです
Wake up, Inspector.
ぐわっ か… 監視官 起きて
（灼）んん… ん？
Huh? Did I doze off?
あれ？　俺 もしかして寝てた？
You were undeniably asleep.
異論の余地なく睡眠中でした
Smile Real Estate
Loan Experts!
Help!
（八(や)ツ俣(また)）た… た… 助けてくれ！
Bring out the guy who lent him money.
（バザロフ）こいつに
金を貸したやつを連れてこい
This is a crime!
これは犯罪だ！
Hey, take it easy.
まあまあ 落ち着いて
あっ
Hit on voice data.
Corresponding individuals identified.
（コミッサ）音声データにヒット
該当する人物を特定
Hitoshi Yatsumata, age 68.
八ツ俣仁志(ひとし) 68歳
Bazarov Triskov, age 50.
バザロフ･トリスコフ 50歳です
In addition to Haneda Park,
Mr. Yatsumata
（雛河）八ツ俣氏は
ここ羽田パーク他―
purchased several registered
rental properties with loans.
複数の物件を
ローンで購入し賃貸登録
Unable to pay the loans,
he mortgaged them.
しかし
ローンが払えなくなり抵当に
Mr. Yatsumata's
failed real-estate investments
（如月）この八ツ俣の
不動産投資失敗で―
led to Mr. Bazarov, who prepaid
three years' rent, being evicted.
３年分の家賃を前払いしていた
バザロフ氏にも退去命令が
Circumstances aside,
this requires suppression.
事情はさておき 要鎮圧事項です
One of Mr. Bazarov's friends is inside.
中にバザロフさんのお仲間が
１人いる
（雛河）えっ？
（如月）何で分かるんですか？
How can you tell?
Tone of voice.
口調です
It doesn't seem like they intend
to harm Mr. Yatsumata.
彼らは八ツ俣さんに
危害を加える気はなさそうだけど…
If this drags out, all their Hues
will suffer. I'll pacify them.
長引けば全員 色相が悪化する
俺がおとなしくさせよう
I'll get something to persuade them with.
じゃ その間に説得材料を用意する
Inspector Ignatov, your orders.
（雛河）あ…
（如月）イグナトフ監視官 指示を
Break in through the empty room next door.
隣の空き部屋を利用し突入する
Won't that endanger the hostage?
人質へのリスクが高いのでは？
It will be fine.
Just trust in Arata.
大丈夫だ 灼の情報を信じろ
（如月）ん…
Don't worry.
You and my brother were both tricked.
（ケイン）心配するな
弟もお前もだまされたんだ
Return my brother's money
and we'll let you go.
（ケイン）弟の金が返ってくれば
解放してやる
I wasn't tricked...!
（八ツ俣）
私は だまされてなんか…
You still don't get it?!
（バザロフ）まだ分かんねえのか！
（ケイン）バザロフ 落ち着け
Bazarov, calm down.
The government won't listen to me
thanks to this idiot.
（バザロフ）このまぬけのせいで
役所も相手にしねえ
My daughter's getting approval
to come join me next month.
来月には娘たちも申請が下り
こっちへ来るってのに…
（ガラスの割れる音）
Public Safety Bureau.
Release Mr. Yatsumata.
（炯）公安局だ
八ツ俣氏を解放しろ
Save me!
（八ツ俣）た… 助けて！
（バザロフ）俺の金が先だ！
Give me my money first!
I'll handle this.
ここは俺がやる
Don't hurt them. Kick them out.
ケガはさせるな つまみ出せ
うおっ ぐわっ
（バザロフ）んっ てい！
Man, it's been too long.
How have you been?
（灼）いやあ お久しぶりです
お変わりありません？
（雛河）あ…
Yes, that's right.
ええ ええ
Ministry of Welfare, like my dad.
あっ 父と同じ厚生省です
（ケイン）えい！　うっ ぐ…
（ケイン）うわっ
（バザロフ）やあ！
（バザロフ）うっ うわ！
うう…
（炯）んっ！
（バザロフ）ああ… ううっ
（ケイン）うう… やあ！
うわ！　うっ…
（炯）ふう… 案外 てこずったな
That was hard.
Well done, sir.
お見事です
ああ…
I've explained this to Immigration.
It won't affect your family's application.
（灼）ご家族の入国申請に
影響が出ないよう―
管理局には
事情を説明してあります
And the Housing Survey Bureau's
agreed to advise you on housing.
それと住宅の件は―
総務省の住宅調査局が
相談に乗ってくれるそうです
（バザロフ･ケイン）えっ？
You risked your lives to get here, right?
命懸けで この国に
たどりついたんだろう？
Don't become a target for enforcement.
執行対象になど決してなるな
As a father,
you need to protect your family.
あなたの家族は
父親である あなたが守るんだ
あっ… ありがとう
Thank you.
（泣き声）
So, the alarm's been lifted.
That's a relief.
警報は解除されたね よかった
No other reports.
Time to start the investigation.
他に通報はなし
これより調査を行う
Investigation?
調査？
Asahi Rick Fellows
What's this?
何ですか？　これ
Data on yesterday's crash.
昨日の事故の情報
The victim Rick's Hue had been
deteriorating for some time.
被害者のリックさん
以前から色相 悪化してたんだ
Since right after he was hired, huh?
トランスポート社に
雇用されてすぐか…
I doubt it's related to the crash.
（雛河）事故とは
関係ないと思いますが
You never know.
なくもないかもしれませんよ
ん…
At present,
（委員）現時点では
後部ハッチ解放と貨物落下が―
the main causes are thought to be
the rear hatch opening and falling cargo.
事故の主な引き金と考えられます
The "main" causes?
（炯）“主な”というと？
Minor engine trouble, malfunctions
in the flight control program, etc., etc.
（委員）
軽微のエンジントラブルに―
飛行制御プログラムの
不具合などなど―
The crash was due to a combination
of factors. I can only call it bad luck.
複合的な要因による事故で…
運が悪いとしか言えません
（リック）うう… すまない
Sorry.
Rick was frightened.
リックさんは怖がってた…
I was told there's a video.
May I watch it?
映像があるそうですが
拝見できますか？
Yes.
はあ…
This is the best video of the crash.
（委員）
一番よく映ってるのは これですね
It's very well shot.
ずいぶん上手に撮れてますね
Enthusiasts hang out on the airport's
observation deck to watch drones come in.
空港の展望台が
マニアのたまり場で…
機体到着まで待機してるんですよ
That must be how they shot this
with perfect timing.
それで どんぴしゃりって
タイミングで撮れたんでしょう
Perfect timing.
どんぴしゃり
I trusted you
because you said it would be fine.
（与根原）お前が
大丈夫だと言うから信じたのに…
Now the Public Safety Bureau
is investigating us!
（鼻をすする音）
（与根原）公安局が―
調査中って何だよ…
As long as your Hue is clear, it's fine.
（些々河(ささがわ)）色相がクリアなら
気にすることはない
え？
くっ… うう…
Hope this makes up for it.
こうして わびに
おごってやってるだろ
This hotel's psychological care
is first-rate.
このホテルのメンタルケアは絶品だ
Like it?
うまいか？
Yeah. It tastes wonderful.
ああ 最高だ
Remember, Yonehara,
忘れるな 与根原
we swore we wouldn't be sheep.
俺たちは羊にはならんと誓った
That we'd succeed in this society
and become foxes.
この社会で成功し 狐になると
（与根原）ハァ… ああ
Yeah.
How's it going,
Seventh Inspector Sasagawa?
（梓澤）調子どう？
セブン･インスペクターの
些々河さん
I'm impressed by your ability,
First Inspector Koichi Azusawa.
（些々河）
ファースト･インスペクター
梓澤廣一(こういち)の腕前 感服しましたよ
The Public Safety Bureau
seems to be chasing us.
なぜか公安局が
追ってるようですが
Not to worry.
ご心配なく
My capable subordinate
has taken care of it.
うちの優秀な部下が―
操作済みですから
（小畑(おばた)の舌打ち）
I am in your debt.
（些々河）恩に着ますよ
Yes. Till next time.
ええ ではまた
The Public Safety Bureau, huh?
公安局ね…
Can you see through my diagram,
detectives?
刑事さん 私のダイヤグラムを
見破れるかな？
フッ
Was there anything unusual
at the time of the crash?
（炯）先日の事故の際
変わったことはなかったですか？
We were just there to film planes.
（ドローンマニア）僕たち
飛行機 撮りに来てるんで
Right?
Yeah.
（ドローンマニア）なあ？
（ドローンマニア）うん
Yeah. We were too focused on
taking pictures to notice anything else.
（ドローンマニア）ああ
それどころじゃなかったよ
写真 撮るのに集中しちゃって
（灼）ん？
They could've just asked an analyst.
（如月）分析官に頼めばいいのに
Apparently, this is how detectives
did it in the old days.
昔の刑事のやり方… らしいです
He filmed it here.
（灼）ここで撮影した
んん…
I knew it.
やっぱり
He couldn't have filmed it
unless he knew it would crash.
落ちると分かってなければ
撮れない
（手をたたく音）
（灼）あっ
You look pale.
（炯）顔が青いぞ
I'm fine.
（灼）大丈夫
Did you Trace the guy who was here?
（炯）ここにいたやつを
トレースしたのか？
I don't have enough data,
so it wasn't clear.
（灼）情報が少なすぎて
はっきりしないけど―
He's tall,
going by the position of the camera.
カメラの位置からして高身長の男
He knew the drone would crash,
and he enjoyed it.
ドローンが落ちると知ってて
楽しんでた
Then he submitted the video he took.
そして
自分で撮った映像を提出した
Why?
何で？
The investigation would end sooner
that way.
そのほうが調査が早く終わるから
The person who orchestrated the crash
was here.
ここに
事故を仕組んだやつがいた…
So, that's their move.
（梓澤）そう来ましたか
What's their deal? They're creepy.
（小畑）何？　あいつら きもっ
No, I find them amusing.
いやいや 面白いじゃない
This is a crime?
（如月）これが事件？
The perpetrator was there?
犯人があそこにいた？
What's all this psychic-sounding
mumbo-jumbo?
何です？　それ
超能力じみたこと言って
It's not ESP. It's a quirk of Arata's.
（炯）超能力じゃない 灼の個性だ
（如月）え…
Special-A-Class Mentalist Skill.
特Ａ級メンタリスト･スキル
Through extreme empathy,
he can cross the mental borderline.
高度な共感により
精神的ボーダーラインを越境する
Huh?
え？
It means he can become another person.
他人になりきるってこと？
Based on circumstances, reasoning,
and statistics.
状況 推理 統計をもとにしてね
Anyone can do it with practice.
練習すれば誰でもできます
（あくび）
But won't becoming
a target for enforcement cloud your Hue?
でも執行対象なんかに
なりきったら―
色相 曇りませんか？
Part of a Mentalist's skill
is making sure that doesn't happen.
曇らないようにするのも
メンタリストのスキルですから
I see. So, what next?
はあ
それで 次は何を？
Questioning Adele Fellows.
（炯）
アーディレ･フェロウズの事情聴取
Who?
（如月）誰です？
（雛河）被害者の奥さん
The victim's wife.
It's late today, though. Maybe tomorrow?
まあ でも
今日は遅いから あしたかな
When I got the call,
（アーディレ）連絡を受けて
まず考えたのは―
my first thought was whether
I'd be able to stay in this country.
この国に
いられるのかと…
Will it hinder my gaining citizenship?
国籍取得に
支障はありますか？
That's the Immigration Bureau's
jurisdiction, but we'll do all we can.
（炯）入国管理局の管轄ですが
我々も最大限 助力します
It appears that your husband's Psycho-Pass
was deteriorating.
（灼）ご主人のサイコパス
悪化してたみたいですけど―
Was he having trouble at work?
お仕事 大変だったんですか？
Yes. He seemed worried about something.
あ… はい
何か悩んでいる様子でした
Any idea what?
“何か”とは？
He didn't talk about work at home.
It was just a feeling I got.
（アーディレ）
仕事の話を家ではしない人で
雰囲気で… としか
May we see your husband's room?
ご主人の部屋 見てもいいですか？
Of course.
（アーディレ）あ… はい
ハァ…
A formula puzzle, huh?
（灼）数式パズルか
（入江）何だ？　ありゃ
What's that?
Based on a formula derived
from the linear equations...
（雛河）空間上のベクトルの
直線方程式を解いた…
OK, got it. That's enough.
分かった 分かった もういい
Your husband was good at puzzles?
ご主人 こういうの得意なんですね
He was a mathematician
in our home country.
（アーディレ）
母国で夫は数学者をしていました
Since coming here, he specialized
in computational finance, right?
この国に来てから
専門は金融工学でしたね
That's right.
はい
Some call him a genius.
天才と呼ぶ人もいます
Pardon me,
but isn't this your second marriage?
失礼ですが 再婚だとか
I lost my spouse in a civil war.
内戦で伴侶を失いました
I met him at an evacuation site.
彼とは避難先で出会って…
He said we should live somewhere
our home wouldn't be destroyed.
二度と家を焼かれる心配のない
場所で暮らそうって
あ… うう…
How long are they going to listen
to sob-stories? Just get it over with.
いつまで
お涙ちょうだい聞いてんだ
おい さっさと終わらせろよ
Easier said than done.
そう言っても…
Well, Hinakawa?
どう？　雛河さん
The internet logs are too clean.
ネットのログも何もなさすぎて
The device at the scene was empty, too.
現場にあったデバイスも
空っぽだった
If he was a mathematical genius,
he'd know they were easy to erase.
数学の天才なら
簡単に消せると分かってた
（雛河）え？
What if he had something
someone would kill him for?
（灼）もし命を狙われる何かを
持っていたら…
Kill?
（アーディレ）命？
（炯）おい 灼
Hey, Arata.
There's nowhere to hide anything
in this room.
この部屋に―
隠す場所はない
（アーディレ）フフッ
（リック）ん…
These flowers are all rare, aren't they?
珍しい花ばかりですね
My husband used holos
to reproduce flowers from his homeland.
夫が故郷に咲いていた花を
ホロで再現したんです
He couldn't get real ones.
本物は手に入りませんから
（雛河）よくできてる
They're well made.
He made them himself?
He could make a living on this.
（入江）自作かよ
これで食ってけるぜ
It was the one hobby my husband had.
夫の唯一の趣味と言えるものです
（においを嗅ぐ音）
Do you mind turning off the flower holos?
花のホロ 消してもいいですか？
Sure.
（アーディレ）ええ
（嗅ぐ音）
フッ… いいにおい
Nice aroma.
These are artificial.
これだけ造花だ
He made those, too. He wanted
his flowers to have fragrance.
（アーディレ）それも夫の自作で
花には香りが欲しいと
Ask permission first, idiot.
あっ バカ 断ってからにしろ
Sorry. I'll put them right back.
あっ すみません すぐ戻しますから
No place to hide a flower
花を隠すには―
better than a flower vase.
花瓶の中ってね
（アーディレ）えっ？
（入江）あ？
He was hiding some kind of data here.
（雛河）何かのデータ 隠してた
You mean my husband's death
wasn't an accident?
夫は
事故ではないんですか？
We don't know yet. We're investigating.
まだ分かりません 調査中です
But if it wasn't...
でも もしそうだったら…
I promise we'll find his killer.
必ず犯人を見つけ出します
Please do.
お願いします
This is quite the encryption.
It'll take time.
大した暗号化ね 時間かかるわよ
May I try?
ちょっといいですか？
Let me see...
えっと…
（キーボードを打つ音）
Oh. Then how about...
（灼）あらま じゃあ…
（キーボードを打つ音）
（灼）うーん
What about this?
こっちか？
It unlocked.
（入江）あっ
（雛河）ひ… 開いた
It's his wife's name.
（灼）奥さんの名前です
"Name"? Those are numbers.
（入江）名前って…
数字じゃねえか
It's a Polybius square.
It substitutes numbers for letters.
（志恩）ポリビオス暗号表
アルファベットを
数字に置き換えたやつ
I'm amazed you figured it out.
よく分かったわね
Just a lucky guess.
（灼）フッ たまたまですよ
（天馬）勘かよ おい
Lucky guess? Seriously?
Now, let's see what's inside.
じゃあ 早速 中身を見てみましょう
What's all this?
（天馬）何じゃ？　こりゃ
Looks like the Hyper Transport Company's
account books.
（雛河）これ ハイパー･
トランスポート社の帳簿ですね
Illegal accounting?
Hidden ledgers for embezzlement or fraud?
不正経理か？
横領や粉飾決算の隠し帳簿？
Nothing like that.
（志恩）そういうのじゃないわね
Pay data for thousands of employees
and mortgage management tables?
関連社員 数千人分の
給与情報と―
住宅ローンの管理表
What did he want to hide this for?
ハァ… こんなもん隠して
何がしたかったんだ？
Mortgages...
住宅ローン…
Is it cause to investigate?
（炯）捜査のネタになるか？
Loans, a crime? You must be joking.
ローンが犯罪？　ご冗談を
Who's in charge of these account books,
anyway?
そもそもの帳簿の管理者 誰です？
Let me look.
（志恩）検索 検索～
One's that guy who was at the scene.
（炯）１人は現場にいた男か
One of Hyper Transport Company's
senior executives.
（灼）ハイパー･トランスポート社
上級役員
Financial Officer Takumi Yonehara.
財務担当 与根原 巧(たくみ)さん
Financial Consultant Tetsuya Sasagawa,
（志恩）同顧問 些々河哲也(てつや)
former chief administrator
of the Urban Housing Finance Corporation.
元総務相 都市住宅公庫 管理長
A textbook case of a golden parachute.
純度100％の天下りね
Same background.
Graduated from the same university.
出身も同じで 大学も一緒
Probably friends.
友人同士かも
ハァ…
Are we going to put the screws on him?
（天馬）あいつを
締め上げるってんですか？
Just rattle him. Follow my lead.
揺さぶるだけだ 適当に合わせろ
Yessir.
へいへい
May I have a moment, Mr. Yonehara?
ちょっといいですか？　与根原さん
What do you want?
ん？　な… 何だよ？
I'm undergoing care!
お… お前ら ケア中に
There were developments in Rick's case.
リック氏の件で進展がありまして
What about him? We only hired him
to follow the anti-isolation policy.
あいつが何なの？
うちは開国政策に従って
雇ってやっただけでしょ
And now you're spending company money
on expensive psychological care?
そういうあんたは
会社の金をくすねて―
高いメンタルケアを
買ってるってわけか？
What was that?
な… 何だと？
Isn't Tetsuya Sasagawa with you?
（炯）些々河哲也さんは
一緒ではないんですか？
Why bring him into this?
えっ な… 何で
あいつの名前が出るの？
Should we really be doing this?
（雛河）これって
まずいんじゃないですか？
Don't worry about it.
だいじょぶ だいじょぶ
We have evidence, Mr. Yonehara.
証拠はあるんです 与根原さん
（与根原）え…
Next, we'll measure the Crime Coefficients
of everyone involved.
次は関係者全員の犯罪係数を測定
Enforcement action may be called for.
もしかすると執行もあるかもなあ
Don't be ridiculous!
You'd never get away with it.
バカ言ってんじゃないよ！
そんなこと許されるもんか！
Aren't you going to question our evidence?
We could be bluffing.
（炯）証拠のほうは
疑わないんですか？
（炯）はったりかもしれないのに
（与根原）えっ？
Thank you for your cooperation.
ご協力 ありがとうございました
Enjoy your psychological care.
よいメンタルケアを～
（与根原）あ…
Even I could tell. We got a reaction.
俺でも分かる 反応ありだ
Too strong a reaction.
反応が強すぎる
He doesn't have the mentality
to take deaths lightly.
人が死んでもいいと思う
メンタルの持ち主じゃない
So, he's not the main culprit.
（炯）主犯は別か
（霜月）ふん！
んっ！
The Hyper Transport Company,
related ministries,
ハイパー･トランスポート社
関連省庁
the Drone Administration Bureau,
and a psychological care center!
ドローン管理局
おまけにメンタルケア施設！
They all complained! What did you do?
クレームの嵐よ！　何をしたの？
Investigated.
調査です
Collected data for crash prevention.
事故防止のためのデータ収集です
Have you no shame?
（机をたたく音）
（霜月）んっ！　しらじらしい！
You have one minute to state
有力省庁の天下り先―
your grounds for making an enemy
of a domestic drone industry leader.
かつ国内ドローン事業トップを
敵に回すだけの根拠
１分で述べよ！
The crash was fabricated
in order to silence the deceased.
（霜月）事故は偽装 目的は口封じ
The principal offenders are two senior
executives of the Hyper Transport Company.
主犯格は―
ハイパー･トランスポート社の
上級役員２人
We believe that the victim, Rick Fellows,
was preparing to blow the whistle on them.
被害者のリック･フェロウズは―
何らかの内部告発を準備していたと
推測されます
Crashing a transport drone
to kill one person isn't realistic.
（霜月）１人を殺すために
輸送機を落としたというのは―
空想的すぎる
But if it's true?
そうではないとしたら
It's not even your job.
あなたたちの仕事ですらない
Tell me why you're fixated on this case.
なぜ この件にこだわるのか
述べなさい
（灼）え…
Well...
えっと…
Because we're detectives.
それは刑事だからです
ん…
Are you stupid?
バカじゃないの
あ…
Understood, ma'am.
We'll abandon the murder angle.
分かりました 課長
（灼）殺人の線は諦めます
（炯）おい
Hey.
Good.
よろしい
That said,
（灼）ただ…
（霜月）ん？
preliminary investigations based on
Bureau regulations take priority.
公安局の規定に基づく
予備調査は―
優先的に
認められているはずです
You're just going to gather data?
（霜月）あくまで
データ収集であると？
Yes, ma'am.
（灼）はい
（炯）規定は守ります
We'll obey regulations.
Too many people start off like that,
but end up wading in too deep.
（霜月）
そうやって深みにはまり―
抜け出せなくなった者は
大勢いるのよ
Approved. But if you break regulations,
be prepared for suitable punishment.
許可する
ただし 規定に反した時は
相応の処分を覚悟しなさい
And you're in charge of preserving
your own Psycho-Passes. Understood?
それと 己のサイコパスは
自分たち自身で守ること
いいわね？
Yes, ma'am.
（炯･灼）了解
Public Safety
has proved surprisingly tenacious.
（代銀）公安局が
予想外に食いついた
Liquidating the block is urgent business.
発生したブロックの解消が急務だな
Judge.
Short-sell the Hyper Transport Company.
（静火）ジャッジ
ハイパー･トランスポート社の
空売り
You wager the company will fail?
（代銀）会社が潰れるほうに
賭けるというのか
Short-selling incurs limitless risks.
空売りのリスクは無限
If the company recovers,
you could easily go bankrupt.
会社が持ち直せば
あなたが破産しかねないわ
At worst, Roundrobin
will take enforcement action against you.
最悪 ラウンドロビンに
執行されるわよ
Judge, please.
（静火）ジャッジをどうぞ
To prevent Sibyl's interference
シビュラの干渉を防ぎ―
and protect Bifrost's interests
is our duty.
ビフロストの利益を守るのが
私たちの使命
Sell transport related stocks.
輸送関連株をセール
If the sale lowers share prices,
（代銀）
セールで株価が下がれば―
the authorities, fearing the crash's
effects, will protect Hyper Transport Co.?
事故の影響を恐れた行政が―
ハイパー･トランスポート社を
守る… か
This has gotten interesting.
面白くなってきたな
Well, Obata? Did you get the information?
（梓澤）どう？　小畑ちゃん
情報 手に入った？
Ages ago, scumbag.
（小畑）とっくの昔だ クズ
I knew it.
やっぱり
Atsushi's son, huh?
篤志さんの息子か
（小畑の舌打ち）
Wonderful.
いいね
Now, how close to us
will he be able to get?
さあ どこまで
我々に近づけるかな？
Our conclusion is the same.
結論は同じ
The crash was planned.
But demonstrating that will be difficult.
事故は仕組まれた
だが立証は困難
If we give up now,
we won't be able to move forwards.
こんなところで諦めてちゃ
先へ進めない
The truth we're looking for
is somewhere much deeper.
俺たちが探す真実は
はるかに深いところにある
At present, your Mental Tracing
is all we can rely on.
現時点で 頼りは
お前のメンタルトレースだけだ
I'll hold your rope.
俺がロープを握る
Do it.
（炯）やってくれ
（灼）フッ
（炯･灼）フッ
The culprit watched Rick die from here,
with a smile on his face.
犯人は ここで―
リックさんが死ぬのを
笑って見ていた
I'm going to find him.
必ず見つけてみせる
We must pursue justice,
even at the cost of a peaceful society.
（朱）たとえ
平和な社会の代償であっても―
正義を失わせてはならない
Whenever those who seek
the same truth appear,
同じ真実を追う者たちが
現れた時―
I decide to entrust my mission to them.
私は彼らに使命を託す決意をした
I believe that they will be the hounds
who will reach
彼らが猟犬となり
見えざる敵にたどりつくことを―
the unseen enemy.
信じている
♪～
Stupid perfection in your own castle
How smart. You cause me to yawn
Look,
The key to the door is in your hand
Don't you let anyone take control
What do you want?
Go get it. Play by your own rule
The winner always controls the game
You stand in your belief
There's no promising future
Always helpless
Crying for the moon
Finger trembles in fear
With the weight of the trigger
There's a way for us
Show them how we fight
Pull the trigger
～♪
I already told you,
I don't intend to compete with you.
（霜月）前に言ったとおり
そちらと張り合う気はないの
I want to trust you.
（宜野座(ぎのざ)）
君を信じたいと思っている
But circumstances may force us
to take action.
ただ状況しだいで
我々も動かざるをえない
Shut up!
I'm telling you I'll honor our deal.
うっさい！
取り引きは守ると言ってるでしょ
Make sure you do your part!
そっちも
なすべきをなしてちょうだい
I'll remember you said that.
（宜野座）その言葉 覚えておくよ
"Psycho-Pass" refers to the measurement
of a person's mind and personality.
This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance
to real persons or groups is coincidental.